var questionsObj = {
  quizName : "Demo Quiz I",
  quizTags : ["Demo"],
  startTime : 1540933200000,
  questionCount : 10,
  questions: [
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 1',
      question: 'Vienna is the capital of?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Vatican City',
        option2: 'Brazil',
        option3: 'Austria',
        option4: 'Netherlands'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Austria'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 2',
      question: 'What is the currency of China Called?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Yen',
        option2: 'Yuan',
        option3: 'Kyat',
        option4: 'Won'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Yuan'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 3',
      question: 'What do France, Portugal, Greece and Italy have in common?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Capital City',
        option2: 'President of the country',
        option3: 'Currency',
        option4: 'National Animal'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Currency'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 4',
      question: 'What is the Capital of Singapore? ',
      options: {
        option1: 'Tampines',
        option2: 'Singapore',
        option3: 'Sengkang',
        option4: 'Jurong West'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Singapore'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 5',
      question: 'Which of these countries currently have more than one capital?',
      options: {
        option1: 'India',
        option2: 'South Africa',
        option3: 'Spain',
        option4: 'Canada'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'South Africa'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 1',
      question: '139 + 235 = ? ',
      options: {
        option1: '372',
        option2: '374',
        option3: '654',
        option4: '244'
      },
      correctAnswer: '374'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 2',
      question: '256 x 513',
      options: {
        option1: '1,31,328',
        option2: '1,30,562 ',
        option3: '30,218',
        option4: '1,32,534'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1,31,328'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 3',
      question: 'Find the next number in the sequence: 4, 8, 12, 20, _____',
      options: {
        option1: '32',
        option2: '24',
        option3: '28',
        option4: '36'
      },
      correctAnswer: '32'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 4',
      question: 'Find the next number in the sequence:3, 6, 11, 18, ____',
      options: {
        option1: '30',
        option2: '27',
        option3: '26',
        option4: '22'
      },
      correctAnswer: '27'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 5',
      question: '1x1x1x1/1+1 = ',
      options: {
        option1: '1',
        option2: '2',
        option3: '3',
        option4: '4'
      },
      correctAnswer: '2'
    }
  ]}

  module.exports.quizQuestions = questionsObj;